oh well our family is all messed up
right now Brendan called me she said
that your father broke up with her what
why it's going to some kind of mid-life
crisis he won't talk to anybody not even
me he ran away this morning ran away
to where
[Music]
oh my god with the hanger really
oh
oh no
oh my God it smells like a hamster feed
oh man it's cold this is so depressing
oh how did you find me
you are literally parked outside the
goddamn house why are you in here I've
been hiding from your grandma because
you broke up with Brenda I didn't mean
to break up with Brenda
so
and now I'm going through some serious
secret life of Baltimore shed you have
no idea
just letting everybody down
I guess that's the way it's supposed to
be
my age
I'm gonna get used to it
I've had Visions dad
I've seen our alternate lives I've seen
you where you look like you are
your life is and and me I have
opportunity sure I have money sure but
I'm empty and sad and tragic kind of
like the way that you are now
I don't want you to
let your second chance of Love walk out
the door
you know what what you're right I'm
gonna need your help okay will you help
me of course if Dad needs help